Hello.
Hey, Maddy.
Amp.
How are we?
Good, thanks you.
Wanna go surfing?
Yeah, how's the how's the swell?
Yeah, nice looking good.
Yeah, it's nice and sunny too, mate.
You might want to...
Yeah.
All right, yeah,
I think I'm gonna need some sandblock.
About there.
I wear sandblock for a year.
Yeah, yeah, I think you will need it,
just a little glare off the water.
Yeah, now it's looking really,
it's very sunny.
I think Melbourne is sunny too.
Yeah, it is. It's looking great out there.
Nice.
How are you guys traveling?
Good, thank you.
Yeah.
Sorry, mate.
Yeah, good to catch up with Matt though,
like he always get us thinking.
Hmm.
Thinking a little bit.
Yeah.
Outside is come.
For sure, for sure, I mean, yeah.
Environment, yeah, yeah, pretty good.
Yeah, I mean, I think, uh...
Yeah,
when we think about the sustainability
thing, like...
Yeah, I don't know what,
what are we using?
Rach and I missed the meeting the other
day,
but we were using Rach and Mindy to kind
of help us put a perspective on what that
sustainability,
like that page could look like,
or we just, we're not looking at that.
Because I do feel like one of the things
that we probably need.
to kind of really test it is that kind of
search bar on the page.
Like that's similar to me,
like the kind of representation of what
the front door would look like. I mean,
perhaps it's not, you know, on every page.
Yeah, in.
Obviously,
you wouldn't want a search bar on every
page. Yeah.
But I guess as a test for this is a sort
of as that green field.
I don't know if it's.
possible. And I suppose, irrespective,
when we're thinking about the new front
Yeah.
door,
at some point we need to evaluate what is
what can we do with, you know,
bliss or whatever it is, or you know,
the front door that we've got now with
the website, you know,
this is the this is the vendor,
what is the Drupal?
Yeah.
in so far as that,
and that's probably coming into that
knowledge base a bit more as well, right?
Yeah, well, I guess that's the plan,
right?
The...
what's in my head for like this defined
stage that we're in is to being able to,
Mm.
you know, we have a set of
Yeah.
Like.
Let's call it use cases because that's
the wording that we've been using.
And a use case is like we're going to
tackle parking infringements.
flow,
like how do we present that information
in because we know from our research and
from the signals that we're getting that
people get confused around the
eligibility, right?
Yeah.
And we're going to cheque the parking
permit or we're going to cheque the whole
suite of
Use cases by intent,
like the best way for us to identify the
intent,
and that's where you know the this search
bar that you're talking about,
like it can help us, you know,
surface that intent in a very like
didactic way, like you you feed.
Yeah.
A problem,
and then they give you another one, so...
I think.
The idea is to be really,
really focused on what is it that we
wanted to build, like, you know, from.
from the discovery and from all the
things that we collected afterwards is
surfacing that intent is one of the
things that we wanted to figure out.
The other one is like routing, like.
figure out like, I'm eligible for this.
Who do I need? What do I,
what do I need for me,
for me to be able to, you know,
complete this? And the other one is like,
how I'm going to go and do it. Like,
that's pretty much.
what we're seeing from the discovery,
right?
Whatever services that we test that one
on, I think we need to focus on, like,
Mm.
figure out how that looks.
and design something that it gonna enable
us to, you know.
put it to the test, like,
that's why this service is so,
Yeah.
so exciting, right?
Like that we can go and do it.
Yeah.
How are we gonna design that? Like, ****,
like,
I would love Mindy and Rachele to help us
with it, you know, but at the same time,
Hey.
they have their own.
like time frame.
So somehow we need to align to what
they're doing.
And I think what they wanted to get out
of from this work is being able to modify
the design principles in the web, right?
Like the style guides and how those
things work. So
Yeah.
Maybe that's how we need to start
connecting. Like, I think...
Mm.
I think that com web looks great,
but I'm not too fuss about like how
that's going to work more than like the
logic that sits behind.
I think what you show us there, Tom,
is like...
That's the logic that we need to figure
out how we how we gonna lift it right
independently if it's just one search bar
or you know.
Different things that they pop up.
I don't know if that answered your
question, but I'll give you more thoughts.
Sort of, yeah. I think, I mean, obviously,
yeah, I think perhaps it's too soon to...
To look at a specific, you know,
iteration of a search bar in.
Yeah.
Yeah, in the mix,
especially if we've kind of, I guess,
yeah, and I, yeah,
I suppose it's just something that's on
my mind, you know, when I think about,
like,
Yeah.
'cause I understand that the current
website has a terrible search kind of
Yep.
experience, so...
Yeah, maybe, maybe we could,
what we could do is like figure out which,
I don't know what.
what is the main thing that we would like
to have in that page.
against what we don't want to have. Like,
I love the other day when you guys were
Hey.
like, ****,
I don't want the phone number or the
Yeah, yeah.
e-mail address in that page.
And that's a win, right?
Yeah, yeah, for sure.
So I think we need to frame it around
that and like whatever it is that we ask.
Designers to help us with.
Maybe.
is the first step towards like how good
looks like rather than, you know,
He.
the full suite of it.
So it could be that is as simple as like
the structure of the content being able
to.
To guide people to this.
Web.
flag, right?
So it's like really lighting content,
Mm.
but the content is super, super tailored.
And then when they get into the web
messenger space,
they're already in and they forgot about
the web page. Like it becomes irrelevant.
Yeah.
If that makes sense.
Yeah, yeah, I think so.
But yeah,
it's probably something that we need to
talk to Dennis around, like...
Mm.
capacity and stuff.
Yeah, so I guess, yeah, I guess. Yeah,
I mean, I suppose if the time's not now,
Yeah.
that's fine.
But I think that when we do have.
When we do have,
when we do start thinking about, okay,
well, okay,
we can look at designer look for it and
Yeah.
then say it's just a search bar on a page,
whether that be contact us or elsewhere
or the homepage or whatever,
that future state of what we do between
contact us, you know,
pay report request and the homepage is I
think kind of that.
together is what the front door will
become.
We'll sort of conglomerate those things.
But then it's like, okay,
Yeah.
once you type in a search,
where is that coming from? You know,
and I don't know whether or not we need
to actually programme in some effort
around.
testing the search function is part of
our, you know, do we need,
you know what I mean,
like testing the web search is we're
testing off platform.
Yep.
Right,
but we're not we're not really testing
the search function on the app on the
website. We don't, I mean,
we certainly haven't discussed doing that
as yet.
Yep, yeah, yeah, so that's...
Um...
For me,
that's the critical part of the design.
Right, so...
Mm.
Honestly,
I don't care if it's infringement,
parking or rates or waste.
No, not fast, like whatever, whatever,
or a mix of all of them, but...
When we start designing that intelligence
from though that that relies on, you know,
accurate information and that relies with,
you know,
Yeah.
being able to call a spade a spade,
and that's...
And those are the two things that are
important out of the testing in my head,
because they're foundational,
they're permanent,
so we can we can fail the test, but say,
like,
we pass we pass this particular feature
or functionality or...
this part worked really well. Well,
let's build on that one, right?
Mm.
And if it wasn't parking, like,
don't care.
But I think authentication needs,
routing needs, knowledge,
those are the essentials, right?
So if we go like really
Amp.
Granular to a particular use case,
like let's dig down to the to the.
to the minimum amount of things that we
can do that they can teach us something.
and that we are able to like update the
content in the web that way or surface
that content that way.
Mm.
But to be like...
To be 100% honest,
like Drupal is really flexible for what I
know, and...
Mm.
The searching is just that.
It hasn't had any love in there.
So, when you go,
when you go and like give them given a
Mm.
given a care and a pod to a particular
set of knowledge,
it should surface like there's nothing
preventing that technology from you from
Mm.
being used.
It's just that nobody have done what
Mmh.
we're doing.
Mm.
That's what I think.
So, yes, yeah, do we do we talk about,
and I think that I know Margo or
Yeah.
someone's talked about the sort of search
feature or something that...
Yeah.
they're doing, want to do something with,
or doing something with, I mean,
do we plan for, like,
should we be thinking about doing an
on-platform search part of, you know,
like, you know, so we're looking at, yeah,
It should,
it should be part of the design, yeah,
yeah.
yeah, for sure, yeah.
And discovery though, right? Like,
do we need to discover, like, is it like,
Um...
I mean, not discovery, but well,
I guess like if we're doing off-platform
search and we got these key terms and
we're using them there,
should we not do them on the website as
well? Yeah, although, but I think they,
I feel like we did talk about this,
how they said that if you use like...
Google AI,
like you just use a different type of
language when you're...
As opposed to.
Like, on a search bar,
people generally took like, yeah,
they might just type in keywords, yeah,
like topics,
keywords around the questions, yeah, true.
Yeah,
so I might bring you to Mira just for one
sec and just to illustrate how I, how I'm.
..
Yep, yep.
Haven't seen this question to be answered
during the define,
and then the design piece of it, so...
Mhm.
Remember that table that I put there in,
are you guys in Mirelle?
No, mate, let's see it's on then,
let me just...
Just one sec.
So it's really granular,
but I think it illustrates really,
really good what we were talking about.
So it might help.
Seeing that that particular task is going
to be covered, I hope.
That.
Yeah, so.
Yeah.
This table that I'm looking at got.
I see where I am.
Yeah, sorry, mate, this is loading. Sorry,
it's loading here.
Oh.
If I can make that one bigger.
Cute this one.
I can see you there, right, so...
Yeah.
What I'm trying to do with this table.
Um...
Each of the roads that you see there in
different colors.
Yeah.
That's what I'm calling the use case,
right? Like, that's what I'm calling,
like, what we gonna try to...
test or that's the route that it's going
to go and based on those contact reasons.
Yeah.
that Tom surfaces for us,
like that sort of a priority around.
Um...
apply for parking permit,
request for a fine, nominate a driver,
blah, blah, blah,
and then information about parking.
So then.
I map it to all the services and that we
got in Salesforce.
This part here when we're going into the
associated knowledge articles.
You can give us a very good signal around
like what is happening on those services.
EE.
And from there you can start developing
some FIQ,
so developing some knowledge around that
particular set of.
use case and then this is coming from
like the information needs based on the
modes like what you see in green there.
Mhm.
This column is the prompt for us to start
defining those information needs.
And what that
What that entitle or that what what
that's gonna mean for design is.
is around the jobs to be done. Like,
is around what the customer is coming
Mmh.
here to do, right?
So you can look at those ones and say,
like, matching with the modes,
this is what good looks like,
because we already did all that work.
This is the information that we need for
it.
This is the way that we can capture that
information, like either in the CRM,
we can do it in Genesis,
we can we can do that,
those columns of where the information is
coming from,
like Matt was saying from anywhere.
And then we do the same for authenticated
needs.
And then we do the same for needs for
support or whatever is that the other
needs that like that mapping that Tom did
on like,
is going to talk to a person or you need
to need to go into the routing of.
of AI only like cell service,
what are the information that the good
looks like,
the acceptable path or the now this is
failure.
We can do those mappings and from that
Mm.
from that exercise you will get your
knowledge.
Needs from the website,
and you can feed that knowledge to the
search, right?
And and that's the part that I'm saying.
Yeah.
feasible in Drupal,
Drupal can pick that information from
Mm.
anywhere,
even if it's if if at the start is going
Yeah.
to be a static table that we feed into it.
And we go like, yeah,
when people ask for these terms or
whatever is that we the rules that we put
in, like look at this table only.
and feed that information, right? So...
Yeah.
I think that.
that exercise of interrogating this list,
because this list is what I'm putting up
there for us to refine, right? Like,
on those test cases,
Mm.
is the requirement for, you know,
the knowledge management or the knowledge
surfacing or supporting this tool that I
see.
Mm.
What it is there today?
Um...
Yeah.
I'm not sure if it's going to help us
very much to improve it or we're going to
go into this rabbit hole with Jasmine and
like, oh no,
we need a big project to change the
search because that, again,
thing doesn't work. So
No, this is good. This is good.
That's how I see it working, right? Like,
we need to come together,
Yeah.
interrogate this list,
because all of those columns are based on
what we discover in discovery,
like what the historical data was telling
us, what?
Tom analysis did for the contacts,
the priority services.
Then we inject the modes and what we
haven't done here is on those mode is
define.
Mm.
But we can map that one to, you know,
the definitions that Dennis was showing
Yeah.
us yesterday, like, for each of the modes,
we got like,
this is a good experience for that mode,
and we use those ones to map to our
Mm.
channel offering and say, like...
In digital, this translate to that,
this translate to, you know,
Mhm.
a no touch or this translate to, and then.
..
Even more granular,
you can start designing those ones and
say,
we're going to define those use cases for
a particular segment of customers that
there's more likely that they're going to
come and do a parking permit.
of I can review. So,
I think that's the part that we're
missing,
like not missing is we haven't got there
yet, because that's the design part,
right? I'm not, I'm not a designer,
Mm.
like I can't do that ****,
but I think this is the work that nobody
Yeah.
had done.
done so far and that's why like the
search is so ****.
Yeah, yeah,
this is the other way of probably a more
needs-based approach as opposed to like
identifying what's broken and what we can
probably see is broken. This is saying,
well, this is what we need, you know.
And then that creates, I guess,
the criteria for the knowledge that feeds
Yep.
the search or anything else. Could also,
you know, like, you know,
Yeah.
help with the digital assistant or,
you know,
like when we need to authenticate.
Because really, theoretically,
Yeah.
what we should be able to get to is a
situation where the majority of contacts
that require assistance
Have, yeah, need authentication, yeah,
right, and you know,
then we can look at how do we do that,
you know,
Yeah.
in the most seamless way possible, yeah,
with context and all that coming across.
Yeah, yeah, no, exactly, and you know,
once we do this one for a couple of
months or so on that particular set of
use cases.
Oh,
you guys are going to start looking at
scaling in Genesis in like a week.
because you already mapped the
similarities on the flows, right?
So it's going to be a matter of, okay,
so yeah,
Mm.
this mode fits into this particular queue
that I've got in Genesis.
Yeah.
Mm.
I'm plugging the FAQ so the knowledge
manager is straight into it and I'm done.
Mm.
You know, like I'm aligned to that.
So you tend to scale a little bit faster
that way too.
But what we need to do now, Jensen,
that brings me to my part of the presser
is like...
This this list is based on, you know,
the problem statement around parking,
but I I think we can we can.
We can open up to like whatever that is.
This is a couple of examples of how it
works. And then we can say, okay,
do you want to bring waste into it?
I don't know,
validate that one with the needs for
information that we're going to have
there,
the amount of services that we're going
to have to surface.
And even if you do it within this list
that it got six different use cases,
we can say like, oh,
the first one might be two.
You.
Or one or three,
like the way the way that I prioritise
those six was because.
It kind of covers quite a lot of modes.
in itself,
although he's talking about parking,
but he's talking about parking compliance,
parking requests for parking officers,
he's talking about parking fines, pay,
he's talking about parking permits,
you know, like
Mm.
And how we surface that one in the
freaking website is like, yeah,
there's an opportunity here.
But that opportunity, you know,
might be as well with rates. I don't know.
Like, I think in the next two weeks,
I would like to bring a lot of people
into this. Like,
I'm going to make it a little bit more
digestible.
But that's what I think.
Mmh.
If.
is good for us to feed into like,
this is the define phase that we got.
Whatever is in here is ready for us to
talk to Mindy, to Rachele, to Dennis,
to whoever is going to help us.
Develop that solution.
Um...
Yeah, that's,
and that's what I mean by like,
the design sprint should be that,
should be a group of people putting
together into like,
You know,
a war room or whatever you call it,
like design sprint,
like let's build this ****.
And you,
you spit something on the other end.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm not sure what.
Yeah, I'm just confused as to what.
What are the activities here? Like,
you know, like, what are we going to do?
Um...
Like, so we got this list here,
which looks good, like,
I think...
so we got this list, you know,
and then this table.
Yeah, it's interrogating, yeah,
it's interrogating those those questions,
right? So those questions are...
Like what I've got here. So yeah,
so knowledge articles.
The cross-mode information need - is that
what you're talking about?
This is just a list of knowledge articles
that they're the most common that.
They are related to those cases, right?
Mm.
So those service type rely on this type
of information.
So we need to analyse what sits behind
those knowledge articles and stuff,
figure out what is.
what is the essence of that knowledge or
what that information needs and how might
we use it for the front end rather than
the back end. So that's one thing.
In this gross mode, needs.
This came out from AI. Like I haven't,
I'm not sure that I have all of them
listed.
It's based on all the analysis that we've
Mm.
done, but.
The work that I think you need to happen
now is interrogating each of those use
cases as unique use case and see the
value of it and see where we need to find
out more or things that are not making
sense to take it to design.
So for example, if
In the first one,
we're talking about what evidence is
required. Like what did that mean?
Do we need to ask that? Maybe not.
Mm.
Maybe like...
is out of the scope for the intelligence
from those.
So there might be things there that
either we need or we miss that we need to
interrogate and then like going beyond
just me putting this one in a table and
So, how do we do that?
say, oh, this is good.
So...
We need to start engaging people, like,
you know, I've had...
I have this draught problem statement
that says that in essence,
the problem statement,
what it's saying is that we wanted to
improve the way customers
arrive at the front door, by intent, by...
I'm really fussy today.
Like the intent was like identify what
they're coming here for,
the eligibility or the...
what this looks like,
how the process work,
and then what do I need to do next, right?
So that's what we surface from discovery
that are the essential parts for the
intelligence from though to provide a
better experience for customers.
Um...
And what we say in that problem statement
is that how might we do that is like we
can look at this parking problems because
they were the strongest signals that we
saw in discovery.
They got a lot of cross-pollination into
the intent that people come here
come to the website and most of it is...
We surface that.
The standardized,
so very common questions generate a lot
of work for us.
and a lot of friction for the customer.
So that's the opportunity there to remove
those.
How we going to be doing that is on those
six use cases. Like, that's the proposal,
right? But...
The.
Before we propose it, we need to, like,
be certain that this is this is adding
that value for it, so maybe bring...
Mm.
Yeah.
Ohh.
How do they use them, right,
for those particular ones?
Run it through Dennis and say, like,
does this make any sense to you?
How will you apply the modes here, right?
Yeah.
Exp.
running it through, I don't know,
Jasmine and...
I mean, I think Glenn is kind of like a,
I mean, yeah,
Glenn's got both that CRO perspective and
also the knowledge. Yeah,
Yeah.
Exactly.
is a really good resource here for this
activity.
Yeah.
Not that we don't want to do it with
others, but I think that, you know,
it's very convenient if we can use Glenn.
Yes.
100%. Yeah.
So that's kind of what I'm thinking next
week.
We could focus on just to unpack that
problem statement and refine it to a
place that we feel comfortable moving
Mhm.
into design, right?
And it might be that it's not just
parking. I think
Jasmine put a comment there is like,
just parking that we're looking at,
awesome. Like,
that's the opening questions that we want.
What do you think?
This is like a subset of,
but the other ones are there, right?
Right.
I mean...
There, there, yeah, there is a big.
They're there,
they're just not even pulling this one in
because...
Exactly. Nobody was doing it. Like,
I brought it up.
I think that's.
So, you know,
the idea is not to do the normal.
Yeah.
So, I'm comfortable with this,
and you know,
focusing on a on a on a specific service
area. I mean, within that, within that,
the parking is massive, right?
We've got and we've got everything that
Yeah.
covers the whole gamut, really, of...
modes and service types that we could
possibly imagine as part of that.
So we can unlock this one.
Yeah.
And if anything, we might be smaller.
It might be a subset of those,
because we don't have the capacity to
design for like those six journeys,
like not journeys,
but like blueprints in there that we
Yeah.
might be looking into. All right, so.
Yeah.
That's the lens, like when...
Yeah,
when we bring people into this sort of
table, it's like with that approach,
this is not finished.
This is like for you to critique and you
know.
Mm.
Move towards, and that's part of kind of.
What I haven't communicated very well
last week on like how that problem
statement.
My.
It might have,
it might have failed to finish, right?
And that's on me.
So that's what I'm trying to change this
week and just start bringing people along
without making it like this big workshop.
Because that that didn't work,
so this is kind of plan B.
Yeah.
Yeah, well, that sounds good. I mean,
yeah, so what are the,
Yeah.
so how do you plan to do that? Like,
and how can we participate?
Yeah, so I, I, I refine,
I refine this this view,
so whatever is that we got here in
Mirelle.
I brought it to Confluence.
I might share my screen instead of
Mhm.
driving you guys in.
I can quickly show you. This is that one.
Yeah.
So, what I did...
Yes,
I put the problem statement in a page.
Like whatever we see in there in Miro,
that's the draught problem statement.
This is all the wording, very dry.
And then Robo did his magic.
Mm.
Here we go, Robo.
And translate that page into this.
Very digestible, that's the identity,
understand, navigate those, those are the.
..
That's all we that's a problem that we're
trying to solve.
Mm-hmm.
And then the six hours of focus,
and here is where we start unpacking.
You know,
how are we going to route people?
How are we going to support them?
The authentication needs those columns
that I show you like.
Yeah.
And then...
This is how.
I don't know what that is.
So.
Each of these projects is one of those
roads.
In the table,
like I got apply from a manager permit,
request a parking permit,
and these are what we need to explore.
Yeah, okay.
And then, and then I got here,
like this is the mapping,
this is this is that table, right?
So we got all the questions and we can
Yeah.
start working with them,
so I need to figure out a way to bring
people along that that is very digestible
and that is action focused on, okay,
this might work or not, so...
You might look different to what we
showed to Glenn than what we showed to
The.
Jasmine.
Yeah.
So, that's what I'm doing next week,
and I'll probably run you guys to first,
Sounds good.
right? So, and bring Mindy,
Mindy and Rachele in, because the, yeah,
the early that we engaged.
So what I'm thinking on Mindy,
Raj and Dennis is like that thinking
about the customer journey,
they're thinking about that design
solution in terms of what they got on
customer segments and how they're going
to be applying. When I talk to Jasmine,
she'll be...
thinking about like, ****,
I'm going to have to redo the website,
how the search is going to work,
where is this going to live,
Mhm.
who is going to be doing that. So,
you know.
Mm.
Juggling all those things.
Yeah.
Which should end up with?
And when we talk to you, it's like, okay,
what are these cues that are giving me
And then we got, yeah.
the most pain?
And we can scale up really quick after
that.
You know what we were talking about,
like that knowledge, sort of face.
Mmh.
Yeah, no, that sounds great, man.
I'm keen to participate in that.
Yeah.
Cool, yeah.
Let's start early next week then.
That sounds really cool.
Sounds good.
Monday, 8 o'clock.
Yeah.
7:30, right? What are these?
Ha ha.
Yeah, right after you ride.
Yeah, well,
it's probably when I'm at my best,
Yeah.
to be honest.
It diminishes as the day wears on, mate.
Yeah, this.
Ohh.
You know,
the grey matter seems to get a bit harder
Ohh, tell me about it.
to call on.
I know.
But yeah, that's what I got on my plate,
gents.
That's that, yeah.
Awesome. Yeah,
I think I need to speak to Tanya about
socialising and getting back in.
And I think now that we've got some sort
Yep.
of,
I think it'd be nice to maybe showcase a
bit of this sort of logic regarding how
we're testing the front door.
with sustainability as part of that.
So I think I'll chat to Tanya.
Yeah.
I had my one-on-one with her yesterday,
but we didn't cover this so much.
Yeah.
But I think that the more we can start to,
I guess, just get her above across.
Cool. Yeah.
I think in terms of,
we're also due to go to the
DCMC did forum on the 24th, I think,
to talk about to talk about the
Yeah.
sustainability stuff,
but whether or not I can actually include
Yeah.
a little bit about the.
The.
Um...
connected channel stuff.
I think I'd like to give them a bit of an
One car that I...
overview.
One card that I put here when we were
talking is like we need to add those
services to this list, right?
Services.
Like.
Like the ones that they're going into the
sustainability.
Yeah.
So start identifying those ones and we
can like highlight it in a different
colour in that.
in that table and say like this is this
is what this
Mm.
Yeah.
Prove of concept, my brain,
and this is what we need.
So this Miro table we've got here,
you got here,
we should add the sustainability.
Yeah.
stuff in there and that's like our first
product really.
Yeah,
like the services that they're going to
be included in. So we can do that mapping.
Yeah.
Against that one too,
so that was part of my to-do, like...
Yeah.
asking Tom or wherever else have they got
those services in.
Darcy.
Yeah, okay. Well,
we should have that information.
Um...
Yeah.
Between Tom and between, you know,
what you what you've received.
Yeah, I just need the,
I just need the list of the services that
are gonna be available, uh,
and then I can map them against CRM and...
Yeah, I don't think we got one from it,
did we? I don't think we,
I don't think we will enough explain what
we mean by services. Like,
Yeah, okay.
what are the actual things that you're
doing?
Yeah, yeah, maybe,
maybe raise that one this afternoon with..
Okay.
.
Yeah, we will. But from what I can gather,
this entire thing is just like...
Done.
Ask them for information.
It's just that or passing it off to
Zapcat.
They're the ones actually doing the
service he stuffs out of cap,
which is why these guys aren't on
Salesforce.
Yeah,
they've been about one existing services
Yeah.
as well, so hopefully that's, yeah, well,
let's see what they say at 2:30.
Yeah, it's a...
So we can,
that's what I map it to the service
catalog.
So,
if it's a city of Melbourne service
should be there,
even if it's not in Salesforce,
like if we come up those those parts.
Um...
So yeah,
maybe we can frame it around like, oh,
have you guys hear about the service
catalog? Yeah. I don't know what that was.
What's that? Oh, here's a link.
Go and have a look.
Yeah.
Um...
Service catalogue is in what you're
talking about, not the Epi thing, are you?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm talking about that one.
This.
OK.
Ahh.
I got stocker presentation this afternoon.
You what?
I got Saka, like is the presentation,
yeah.
Ohh, really? Yeah, the kids.
Yeah, it's gonna be fun.
What time is that?
Five.
Nice.
Yeah, beautiful day for it, man.
Great day for it.
Did I tell you guys about the last game?
No.
Huh?
They play,
they play the last game against Ocean
Grove, which is like their nemesis.
They've been,
Yeah.
they've been beating them all season,
right? Like, badly. They were so scared,
Mhm.
like, oh,
we're going to get beaten again in the
last one, I think.
The previous one was like 6-4 or
something.
Mm.
So they were all,
even the coach though was like, yeah,
0 confident.
And they won by one goal.
Oh, nice.
And Dante scored that goal,
so he's it was, yeah, and Tommy, yeah,
Huge, that would have been.
Were you there?
yeah,
it was a and Tommy was a was a wall into
the fence,
so he prevent all the goals like, yeah,
Yeah.
they couldn't be happier. So, yeah,
they all spot.
No, it's awesome, man.
Really looking forward for that
presentation, right?
Ohh, that's cool.
So this is this is in Power BI Server.
Mm.
Amp.
And it show you all about the service
catalog, alright?
Mm.
So it gives you the profile and the
glossary.
Is it working?
I don't know, but anyway, so...
If it's a service that is in the city of
Melbourne, should be here, all right,
Yeah.
in draught form or whatever, so we can,
and it is searchable by branch as well,
so we should be able to map up to
whatever is that.
the sustainability branch is going to be
doing. And we just got a starting point.
We start mapping things, right?
And if it's not CRM, what are this,
how do you count those services?
How are you doing it at the moment?
And that could be like really good.
Data for us too, like, yeah,
we testing outside CRM too.
Yeah.
Wow.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah,
so we can point them out to here and say
like if you don't know what your service
is.
Name looks like it should be there,
like sustainability and climate
resilience.
I don't know why it's not driving.
Mm.
Anyway.
Okay, yeah,
I'm not as familiar as I probably should
I want.
be with the service catalog.
I've never heard of it until now,
but it looks like a good idea.
Yeah,
so they did a similar design approach to
what the...
What they have done with their customer
segmentation as well,
so they create services profiles and they
got, you know...
Mm.
They got different, different families,
not, I don't think I call it families,
they call it groups or areas,
and they're classified into like customer
facing and internal facing,
or I think there's another category there
too, but yeah, it's...
Mm.
It's...
Is our way out to, you know,
validate whatever it is that we're doing
that, okay, it's mapping to that, right?
We're not talking about something new.
Yeah.
Yeah, that makes sense. That makes sense,
definitely.
Yeah, so yeah,
that's probably a task for this afternoon
as well with the other team.
Lovely, alright.
That sounds good, buddy.
Leave it.
Leave you too, gents.
Thanks, mate.
Enjoy your afternoon and the presentation.
Have fun.
Will do. Bye.
Yeah.
Weeks.